

## Endro Mono

Insightful Information Technology Manager with 9 years of IT Leadership experience including infrastructure oversight and application support. Proven leader in directing operations, maintenance and support of systems. Instructs and Leads IT staff members in supporting hardware, software, and network infrastructure. Actively work with executives to determine and implement technology needs.

# Work Experience



IT Manager • futuregate

Oct 2014 - Mar 2018

- Plans, executes, and oversees IT projects, ensuring they stay on schedule and within budget.
- Ensuring these systems are up to date, secure, and functioning properly.
- Delegating tasks, providing guidance, and ensuring the team has the resources they need to succeed.



IT Staff • morodadi farm

Nov 2009 - Feb 2014

- Maintain existing systems, and ensure the smooth operation of daily technology needs.
- Install and con gure software and hardware.
- Provide technical support to staff regarding software and hardware.

### Education



Jun 2004 - Feb 2009

#### Gajayana University

Computer Science

## Skill

- IT Project & Program Management
- IT Business Analytics
- IT Product Management
- IT Security Management
- Agile methodology in Project Management
- Full-Stack Development (Front-End Development and Back-End Development)
- Cloud Computing
- REST APIs
- Team Management
- Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- Application Programming Interfaces (API)
- Development and Operations (DevOps)
- Source code management (SCM)
- Distributed version control systems (DVCS/Git)

# Language

- Bahasa Indonesia Native
- English Professional

#### Phone & Email

- +6282244604125
- endro.mono@outlook.com

- Quality Assurance (QA) (Testing: Katalon, Selenium, Postman)
- UI/UX Design
- Web Development Languages

(TypeScript [VueJS, NextJS, EmberJS, ExpressJS, NestJS],

Django, PHP [Laravel, CakePHP, Wordpress])

Mobile Development Languages
 (Flutter, TypeScript [React Native, ionic])

• Back-End Development Languages

(Python, Java, C#, Golang)

• Database Administration

(MySQL, MS SQL Server, Oracle, MongoDB, PostgreSQL)

• Project Management Tools (Jira, Trello)

- Automation Configuration Tools
  (Ansible)
- Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) (Jenkins, GitHub Actions)
- Enterprise Resource Planning
- Content Management Systems (CMS)